rypmarketing.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy

### We won't share your contact information or other personal details with any 3rd party.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at mail@rypmarketing.com. 

At www.rypmarketing.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by www.rypmarketing.com and how it is used. 

**Personal Information**  
All personally identifiable information you may provide to use is stored securely and is not shared with third-parties. We use this information only to contact you regarding our products and services. 

**Log Files & Analytics**  
Like many other Web sites, www.rypmarketing.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files and analytics records includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies**   
www.rypmarketing.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.
